Register of the Stanford University Institute of Hispanic American and Luso-Brazilian Studies Collection, 1954-1965
Hoover Institution Archives
Stanford University Institute of Hispanic American and Luso-Brazilian Studies Collection,
1954-1965
54003
Stanford University Institute of Hispanic American and Luso-Brazilian Studies
852 manuscript boxes, 6 card file boxes (357.8 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Pamphlets, clippings, and serial issues, relating to political, social, and economic conditions in Latin America, Spain, and Portugal. Collected by the Institute of Hispanic American and Luso-Brazilian Studies at Stanford University
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is stored off-site. It may be possible to have a limited number of boxes brought to the archives reading room for examination. A minimum of two days notice is required. Please contact the Hoover Institution Archives for further information.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1954.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content of Collection
Pamphlets, clippings, and serial issues, relating to political, social, and economic conditions in Latin America, Spain, and Portugal. Collected by the Institute of Hispanic American and Luso-Brazilian Studies at Stanford University.
Access Points
Latin America; Latin America--Economic conditions--1945-; Latin America--Politics and government--1948-; Latin America--Social conditions--1945-1982; Portugal; Portugal--Economic conditions--1918-1974; Portugal--Politics and government--1933-1974; Portugal--Social conditions; Spain; Spain--Economic conditions--1918-1975; Spain--Politics and government--1939-1975; Spain--Social conditions
Series Description
- Subject File, 1954-1964. (Box Box No. 1 -771.)
  Clippings, press releases, reports and studies collected by the Institute of Hispanic American and Luso-Brazilian Studies at Stanford University for the study of developments in Latin America, Spain, and Portugal. Newspapers from which clippings were taken include Copley News, Diario las Américas, Excelsior, Foreign Commerce Weekly, Foreign Radio Broadcasts, El Mundo, Visión, El Dia, La Prensa, Peruvian Times, Embajada de Colombia, Estrella de Panama, El Tiempo, El Comercio, and others. Arranged chronologically by month and thereunder alphabetically by country.
- Miscellaneous, 1961-1967. (Box Box No. 772 -777.)
- Card Files. (Box Box No. 778-783.)
  Information file on people, political parties, and governments in South America, Central America, and the West Indies. Also includes Deadline Data on World Affairs.
Container List
- January 1954
  - Argentina (Box 1.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic
  - Mexico
  - Mexico (Box 2.)
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
- February 1954
  - Argentina (Box 2.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama, (2 envelopes) (Box 3.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic
  - Mexico
  - Peru
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay and Paraguay
  - Venezuela
- March 1954
  - Argentina (Box 4.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic (Box 5.)
  - Mexico
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
- April 1954
  - Argentina (Box 6.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes)
  - Central American and Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic
  - Mexico (Box 7.)
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
- May 1954
  - Argentina (Box 7.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Central America and Panama, (2 envelopes) (Box 8.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic
  - Mexico
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
- June 1954
  - Argentina (Box 9.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Central America and Panama, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Equador
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Paraguay and Uruguay (Box 10.)
  - Peru
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain and Portugal
  - Venezuela
- July 1954
  - Arentina (Box 10.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic
  - Mexico
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru, (3 envelopes) (Box 11.)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain and Portugal
  - Venezuela
- August 1954
  - Argentina (Box 11.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Central America and Panama
  - Central America and Panama (Box 12.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain and Portugal
  - Venezuela
- September 1954
  - Argentina (Box 12.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic
  - Mexico (2 envelopes) - one Sept.-Dec. (Box 13.)
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
- October 1954
  - Argentina (Box 13.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 14.)
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic
  - Mexico
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
- November 1954
  - Argentina (Box 14.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia (Box 15.)
  - Cuba
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic
  - Mexico
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
- December 1954
  - Argentina (Box 15.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Central America and Panama (Box 16.)
  - Cuba
  - Mexico
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - International
  - Columbia University: Bicentennial Conference on Latin America (1954) envelopes I-III
  - Columbia University: Bicentennial Conference on Latin America (1954) envelopes IV-XIV (Box 17.)
  - Papers concerning the Tenth Conference of American States, Caracas Venezuela - March 1954 (Box 18.)
- January 1955
  - Argentina (Box 18.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes) (Box 19.)
  - Cuba
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic
  - Mexico
  - Nicaragua
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain (2 envelopes) - one with material concerning the transliteration of Arabic names
  - Venezuela
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- February 1955
  - Argentina (Box 19.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Chile (Box 20.)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti and Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico
  - Nicaragua
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela (Box 21.)
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- March 1955
  - Testimony given on behalf of Congress of Industrial Organizations to House Committee on Agriculture of the U.S. Congress by Milton Plumb as Secretary of U.S. Section of the Joint U.S.-Mexico Trade Union Committee. Testimony concerns importation of Mexican laborers for work on U.S. farms. (Box 21.)
  - Argentina
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti
  - Mexico (Box 22.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- April 1955
  - Argentina (Box 22.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Central America (Guatemala, Honduras, El Salvador) (Box 23.)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti
  - Mexico (2 envelopes) 2nd one marked background material
  - Panama
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain (Box 24.)
  - Venezuela
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- May 1955
  - Argentina (Box 24.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama, (2 envelopes) (Box 25.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal (Box 26.)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
  - International
- June 1955
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 26.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes) (Box 27.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Guatemala, Honduras, El Salvador
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti
  - Mexico
  - Paraguay and Uruguay (Box 28.)
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
  - International
- July 1955
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 28.)
  - Bolivia (Box 29.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic (Box 30.)
  - Ecuador
  - Haiti
  - Mexico
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain (Box 31.)
  - Venezuela
  - International
- August 1955
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 31.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Brazil (Box 32.)
  - Central America and Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic and Haiti
  - Ecuador
  - Mexico (Box 33.)
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
  - International
- September 1955
  - Argentina (Box 33.)
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 34.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Cuba (Box 35.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru (Box 36.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
  - International
- October 1955
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 36.)
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 37.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia (Box 38.)
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Panama
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal (Box 39.)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain (Morocco)
  - Spain, U.S., U.N., U.S.S.R., Franco-Hispanidad
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- November 1955
  - Argentina (Box 39.)
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 40.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Cuba (Box 41.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica and Nicaragua
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - Guatemala and El Salvador
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay and Uruguay
  - Peru (Box 42.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Venezuela
  - International, (2 envelopes)
  - International Inter American Press Association
- December 1955
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 42.)
  - Bolivia (Box 43.)
  - Brazil
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 44.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International
  - International (Box 45.)
- January 1956
  - Argentina - two copies of Esto Es (magazine) (Box 45.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 folders)
  - Costa Rica, Nicaragua
  - Chile (Box 46.)
  - Colombia
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain (Box 47.)
  - Spain correspondence
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International Territorial Waters (January - March 1956)
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- February 1956
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 47.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 48.)
  - Costa Rica and Nicaragua
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba (Box 49.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain (Box 50.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- March 1956
  - Argentina Supplementary (Box 50.)
  - Argintina (2 magazines) Comments on Argentine Trade, Europa, Archiv
  - Argentina
  - Bolivia (Box 51.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (5 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica, Nicaragua
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic (Box 52.)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International
- April 1956
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 53.)
  - Argentina Supplementary
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica and Nicaragua
  - Chile (Box 54.)
  - Colombia
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico (Box 55.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - International (Box 56.)
- May 1956
  - Argentina (Box 56.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica, Nicaragua (Box 57.)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru (Box 58.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International
- June 1956
  - Argentina (Box 58.)
  - Boliva (Box 59.)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba (Box 60.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua (Box 61.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - International
- July 1956
  - Argentina (Box 61.)
  - Bolivia (Box 62.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador (Box 63.)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (7 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain (Box 64.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International
- August 1956
  - Argentina (Box 64.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia (Box 65.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 66.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela (Box 67.)
  - International
- September 1956
  - Argentina (Box 67.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes)
  - Brazil (Box 68.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua (Box 69.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes) (Box 70.)
  - Venezuela
  - International
- October 1956
  - Argentina (Box 70.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 folders)
  - Brazil (Box 71.)
  - Chile (August - October)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 72.)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes) (Box 73.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (4 envelopes)
  - Uruguay (Box 74.)
  - Venezuela
  - International
- November 1956
  - Argentina (Box 74.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes) (Box 75.)
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico (Box 76.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela (Box 77.)
  - International
- December 1956
  - Argentina (Box 77.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia (Box 78.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador, (2 envelopes)
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 79.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain (Box 80.)
  - Uruguay, (4 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - International
- January 1957
  - Argentina (Box 80.)
  - Bolivia (Box 81.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador (Box 82.)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (5 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes) (Box 83.)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay (Box 84.)
  - Venezuela
  - International
- February 1957
  - Argentina (Box 84.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia (Box 85.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Mexico (Box 86.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International
- March 1957
  - Argentina (Box 87.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 88.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Mexico (Box 89.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Spain (Box 90.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International
- April 1957
  - Argentina (Box 90.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Brazil (Box 91.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico (April - May), (4 envelopes) (Box 92.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain (Box 93.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International
- May 1957
  - Argentina (Box 93.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Chile
  - Chile (Box 94.)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico (3 folders, one containing the Petroleum Press Service) (Box 95.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico (Box 96.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International
- June 1957
  - Argentina (Box 96.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil (Box 97.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Dominican Republic
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 98.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes) (Box 99.)
  - Venezuela
  - International
- July 1957
  - Argentina (Box 99.)
  - Bolivia (Box 100.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia April - July (Economical)
  - Costa Rica (Box 101.)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru (Box 102.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - International
- August 1957
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 103.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Colombia (Box 104.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 105.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain (Box 106.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- September 1957
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 106.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes) (Box 107.)
  - Colombia
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala (Box 108.)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (5 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru (Box 109.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International (Box 110.)
- October 1957
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 110.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Chile
  - Chile (Box 111.)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 112.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (5 envelopes) (Box 113.)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay (Box 114.)
  - Venezuela
  - International
- November 1957
  - Argentina (Box 114.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes) (Box 115.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti (Box 116.)
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (5 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Portugal, (3 envelopes) (Box 117.)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International
- December 1957
  - Argentina (Box 117.)
  - Bolivia (Box 118.)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 119.)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico (5 weeks)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal (Box 120.)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela
  - International
- January 1958
  - Argentina (Box 120.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Brazil (Box 121.)
  - Chile
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 122.)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico (Box 123.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay